That was kind of fast, right?
Well, that's how we like to.
Bro, we have bought one of Europe's leading tech companies,
with almost 100 million customers.
And over 2,000 employees,
our company at this scale moves at this speed.
Here are some examples.
It took us five years to reach 10 million customers.
Now we're adding 10 million every two months.
Instead of reducing head count,
we added another 500 employees and launched.
Scooters and who delivery in 74 cities in 12 months.
But that wasn't enough.
So we launched car sharing with folks drive.
And that took us four months.
Months and groceries delivery followed just one month later.
That's two new business lines in five months.
How did we do it?
Well, we don't spend time on bureaucracy.
Instead, we move across into more teams.
Teams, everybody acts like an owner.
So a 13 owners launched both markets in one month.
So when others are doing this.
We're doing this.
As the company grows, so did we.
I started as a customer support specialist.
And now I'm originally lead.
And I started as a recruiter.
And now I'm a global recruiter for manager.
And I've been here for four and a half years.
Which is a bullet average.
That's one and a half years more than the industry average.
And I drew and bold when it was just a small story on startup.
And now it's the world's fastest growing money to platform.